

# HIRAS PARASIAN DOLOKSARIBU

081388981122 | hirasparasian@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hiras-parasian-doloksaribu/ | https://github.com/HirasParasian

Bekasi, Indonesia

My journey as a Fullstack Developer has equipped me with a comprehensive skill set and a deep understanding of the entire software development lifecycle. On the front-end, I am proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, along with modern frameworks such as ReactJS, React Native and NextJS. On the back-end, I have experience working with technologies such as Node.js and .NET. I am well-versed in server-side logic, SQL databases, database integration, and API development, ensuring the scalability and performance of web applications.

# **Work Experiences**

#### PT. Deltadata Mandiri - South Jakarta, Indonesia

Nov 2022 - Present

Full-Stack Developer

- Developing, and maintaining web applications from start to finish, including user interfaces, business logic, and database integration.
- Performing front-end development using HTML, CSS, CSS Framework like Bootstrap and JavaScript, along with frameworks like React, Next.
- Implementing server-side programming using languages such as Node.js, C#.

## PT. Konsultan Sistem Manajemen Indonesia - Cileungsi - West

May 2022 - Nov 2022

Java, Indonesia

Full-Stack Developer

- Developing, and maintaining web applications from start to finish, including user interfaces, business logic, and database integration.
- Performing front-end development using HTML, CSS, CSS Framework like Bootstrap and JavaScript, along with frameworks like React, Next.
- Implementing server-side programming using languages such as Node.js, C#.

### PT. READERZEN Tanggap Literasi - South Jakarta, Indonesia

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Wordpress Developer

### TOUCHÉ Development Center - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

May 2021 - Jul 2021

Twitter & Web Team

# **Education Level**

### Universitas Advent Indonesia - West Bandung Regency, Indonesia

Jul 2018 - May 2022

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.92/4.00

Outstanding Student with The Highest GPA (4.00) at 5th Semester & 7th Semester

## SMK Negeri 5 Kota Bekasi - Bekasi, Indonesia

Jun 2014 - Aug 2017

Industrial Electronics Engineering

# Bootcamp in Full-Stack Developer

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

· Responsive Website

**Fazztrack** 

- · Backend with Node.js & Express.js
- Frontend with React.Js & Next.Js
- · Mobile Development With React Native

## Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Projects: PT. Pertamina EP (2023): Create Work Program & Budget Web Application
- Projects: PT. Borneo Indobara (2023): Bug Fixing at PTM Aplication Coal Chain Management Borneo Indobara
- Projects : Satu Data Indonesia (2023): Bug Fixing at CRM Aplication Satu Data Indonesia
- Projects: PT. Astra Honda Motor (2022): Create Career Managemet Online Module
- Certifications ⊚ (2021): Responsive Web Design FreecodeCamp
- Certifications ⊚ (2022): IT Specialist HTML5 Application Development by Certiport A Pearson VUE Business
- Publications ⊚ (2022): Komparasi Algoritma Data Mining Untuk Analisis Sentimen PeduliLindungi
- Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS, React Native, ExpressJS, C#
- Interest: Fullstack Developer, Frontend Developer, Analyst